# **Daniel Chavez**

2047212248 dchavez3395@gmail.com Winnipeg, Manitoba

#### **Summary**

I am a self motivated Web Developer from Manitoba, with years of experience with client work, and dealing with and negotiating complex issues. I am passionate about tech, and have a penchant for developing customized interfaces that factor in unique demands for accessibility, reachability and security. I have an organized approach to meeting multiple, concurrent deadlines with experience working under pressure.

#### **Experience**

# **Birchwood Credit Solutions**

Special Finance Manager, Winnipeg

11/2018 - 07/2021

- Built strong client relationships and provided high value-adding services
- · Interviewed clients, verified Credit history and offered options based on their situation
- Wrote, negotiated and finalized Sales Contracts
- Emphasized product features based on customer's needs

#### **Birchwood Nissan Brandon**

Business Development Manager, Brandon, Manitoba

01/2018 - 11/2018

- Coordinated innovative strategies to accomplish marketing objectives and boost long-term profitability.
- Developed and implemented favorable pricing structures balancing firm objectives against customer targets.
- Collected and responded to user feedback through iterative improvements to site structure and content.
- Planned and executed website editorial schedule by collaborating with designers, web developers, marketing and sales staff.
- Converted design assets into component-based HTML, CSS and JavaScript.
- Developed and implemented WordPress sites, themes and plugins.
- Referenced web analytics reporting to enhance designs and improve site performance.
- Collaborated with end users on project specifications, strategy and execution to build new WordPress pages and update existing ones.

#### **Birchwood Nissan Brandon**

Sales Consultant, Brandon, Manitoba

05/2015 - 01/2018

- Bronze Nissan Club Excellence Winner for 2016
- Highest closing ratio in the store for 2016, 2018
- Identified and qualified client's needs, developed sales strategies and negotiated profitable projects with a high success rate
- Provided repeat clients with exceptional care and attention.

#### Skills

HTML5, CSS, SASS/SCSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, jQuery, Vue.js, Node.js, Express.js, EJS, WordPress, SQL, Git, GitHub, JSON, Photoshop, Responsive Web Design, Programming, Problem Resolution, Communication skills, Negotiation, Bilingual, Microsoft office, Critical Thinking

#### Education

# **High School**

Crocus Plains Regional Secondary School, Brandon, Manitoba 06/2013

# Languages

English, Spanish

#### References

### Cierra Waddell-Hodgson

General Sales Manager

Birchwood Nissan Brandon

Phone: 204-573-7460

email: cierra.waddell@hotmail.com

## **Brady Sobering**

Sales Manager

Birchwood Nissan Brandon

Phone: 204-612-2497

email: brady.sobering@gmail.com

## **Cory Creighton**

Finance Manager

Birchwood Nissan Brandon

Phone: 204-724-7225

email: corycreighton@hotmail.com